in the last video you saw how to compute
在上一个视频中 你了解到了如何计算出
the prediction on a neural network given
神经网络的预测值 它是针对于
a single training example in this video
单一的训练样本而言的 在这个视频中
you see how to vectorize across multiple
你将了解到如何向量化计算
training examples and the outcome will
多个训练样本上的预测值的过程 并且该过程
be quite similar to what you saw for
与你在logistic回归当中所见到的很类似
logistic regression where by stacking up
在logistic回归中 我们通过将
different training examples in different
不同的训练样本组合成
columns of the matrix you'll be able to
矩阵的不同列 来得到我们从
take the equations you have from the
上一节的视频中推导出的
previous video and with very little
各个等式 而且我们只需对它们做出
modification change them to make the
很少的修改 就可以让
neural network compute the outputs on
这些公式适应于神经网络 并计算出输出值
all the examples on pretty much all at
这种计算是几乎同时在
the same time so let's see the details
所有训练样本上进行的 让我们来看一下
of how to do that
如何具体地去实现它
these were the four equations we have
这些是我们从上一节视频中得到的
from the previous video of how you
四个等式 它们给出了
compute Z 1 a 1 Z 2 and a 2 and they
计算出Z1 a1 Z2和a2的步骤 并且它们
tell you how giving an input feature
让你知道给定单个的输入特征向量X时
vector X you can use them to generate  a
应该如何进行计算
2 equals y hat for a single training
才能得出a2 亦即y hat
example now if you have M training
而如果现在有m个训练样本的话
examples you need to repeat this process
你就需要重复这个过程
for say the first training example X
比如对于这第一个训练样本x_1
superscript round records one to compute
我们用它来计算
Y hat one that's the prediction on your
y_hat_1 亦即预测值 该预测值是
first training example then X2 to use
在第一个训练样本上得出的结果
that to generate prediction y hat two
然后使用x_2来生成预测值y_hat_2，
and so on down to XM to generate a
等等一直到用x_m生成
prediction Y hat M and so in order to
y_hat_m 并且为了
write this with the activation function
和之前约定的符号规范达成一致
notation as well I'm going to write this
我要把它写成
as a two square bracket round bracket
a[2](1)
one and this is a two two and A to M so
这是a[2](2)和a[2](m)
this notation a square bracket two round
所以这个符号a[2](i)中
bracket I the round bracket I refers to
(i)是指
training example I and the square
第i个训练样本
bracket 2 refers to layer 2 ok so that's
而[2]是指第二层 所以这就是
how the square bracket in the round
[] 和 ()
bracket indices work and so the suggest
所代表的含义 并且这也表明了
that if you have an unvectorized
如果你有一个非向量化形式的
implementation and want to compute the
实现并且想要计算出
predictions for all your training
所有样本上的预测值
examples you need to do for I equals 1
你需要做的就是让i从1
to m then  basically implement these
遍历到m 然后实现这
four equations ready meet I guess z1 i
准备好的四个等式
equals w1 x I plus b1 and a1 I equals
亦即z[1](i)=w[1]x(1)+b[1]
sigmoid z 1 i and z 2 i equals W 2 a 1 i
a[1][i]=sigmoid(z[1](i))
plus b 2 and a 2 i equals sigmoid of z 2 i
z[2](i)=w[2]a[1](i)+b[2] 而a[2][i]=sigmoid(z[2](i))
right so it's basically you know these four equations on top
总而言之 我们需要对上面的这四个方程中
and adding the superscript round bracket i to all the
所有依赖于训练样本的变量
variables that depend on the training
添加一个上标(i)
example so adding the superstream round
具体而言 我们需要将(i)
bracket I to X and Z and a if you want
添加到x z和a上 如果你想
to compute all the outputs on your M
一次性计算m个训练样本上的所有输出的话
training examples what we like to do is
一般而言就会需要
vectorize this whole computation so as
向量化整个计算过程
to get rid of this for loop and by the way
从而能够避免使用这个for循环 顺带一提
in case it seems like I'm guessing a lot
虽然看起来我正在使用很多
of nitty gritty linear algebra it turns
很乱很糟心的线性代数
out that being able to implement this
但是在当今这个深度学习的时代中
correctly is important in the deep
能够正确地实现这些东西是重要的
learning era and we actually chose the
事实上我们也针对这个课程
notation very carefully for this cost
来认真地选择了符号规范
that make these accusations as as easy
并且使这些向量化尽可能的容易
as possible so I hope that great through
所以我希望你能够通过理解这些
this nitty-gritty will actually help you
又乱又糟心的公式
to more quickly get correct
来更快地得以
implementations of these advents working
正确地实现这些算法
all right so let me just copy this whole
接下来让我复制
block of code to the next slide and then
这整个代码块到下一个幻灯片 然后
we'll see how to vectorize this
我们将看到如何向量化它们
so here's we had from the previous line
那么这是我们从前一张幻灯片中
with a for loop going over all M
得出的for循环
training examples so recall that we
它用来遍历所有m个训练样本 还记得
define the matrix X to be equal to our
我们定义矩阵X等于
training examples stacked up on in these
这些训练样本，将它们在矩阵的列中
columns like so so take the training
进行组合，所以拿训练的样本
examples spat them in columns so this
将它们组合在列中，所以
becomes a n or maybe NX by M
这成为n维或n_x乘以m
dimensional matrix I'm just going to
维矩阵 我只是告诉你
give away the punchline and tell you
这个最后的结果 然后告诉你
what you need to implement in order to a
你需要实现什么，
vectorized implementation of this for
以便对此for循环进行向量化实现
loop turns out what you need to do is
事实上你需要做的是
compute capital Z 1 equals W 1 X plus B
计算Z[1]等于w[1]x + b[1]，
1 capital A 1 equals sigmoid of Z 1 then
A[1]等于sigmoid(Z[1])
tap code v2 equals W 2 times a 1 plus B
那么Z[2]等于w[2]*A[1] + b[2]，
2 and then a2 equals sigmoid of V 2 so
然后a[2]等于sigmoid(z[2])。
if you want the analogy is that we went
所以以此类推，我们想要，
from lowercase vector X s to this
从小写的向量x
capital case X matrix by stacking up the
到这个大写字母X矩阵，通过组合这些
lower case X's in different columns if
小写x向量在不同的列中，
you do the same thing for the Z's so for
如果你为z做同样的事情，
example if you take Z 1 1 z 1 2 and so
所以，如果你采取z[1](1)，z[1](2)等等，
on these are all column vectors up to Z
这些都是直到z[1](m)的列向量
1 M right so that's this first quantity
所以这是第一个数量，
but all M of them and stack them in
但是他们中的所有m都将它们
columns then this gives you the matrix Z
组合在列中，那么这就是矩阵Z[1]。
1 and similarly if you look at say this
同样地，如果你看这个
quantity you can take a 1 1 a 1 2 and so
数量并且采取a[1](1)，a[1](2)等等
on an a 1 M and stack them up in columns
a[1](m)并将其组合在列中，
then this just as we went from lower
那就这样，就像我们从小写的x那样
case X to capital case X and low kcee -
一直到矩阵X以及从小写字母
Catholic 8 Z this goes from the lower
z到矩阵Z，这是小写的a，
case a which are vectors to do some
它们是向量，
capital a 1s over there and similarly
同样
for Z 2 and a 2 alright they're also
对于Z[2]和A[2]，他们也是这样得的
attained by taking these vectors and
通过将这些向量
stacking them horizontally and taking
水平组合在一起，然后通过
these vectors and stacking them
这些向量的
horizontally in order to get Z Capital Z
水平组合，以获得矩阵Z[2]
2 and chapter 2
和矩阵A[2]
one of the property of this notation
这种符号可能让你想到
that might help you to think about it is
它的其中一个作用就是
that these matrices say Z and a
正是这些矩阵，Z和A
horizontally we're going to index across
我们将通过训练样本来进行索引，
training examples so that's why the
所以这就是为什么
horizontal index you know corresponds to
水平索引对应于
different training examples is sweep
不同的训练样本，这些训练样本
from left to right you're scanning
是你从左一直到右边
through the training set and vertically
扫描训练集而得到的  而在垂直方向
this vertical index corresponds to
这个垂直索引对应于
different nodes in the neural network so
神经网络中的不同节点
for example this node this value at the
所以例如，这个节点，该值
topmost top left corner the matrix
位于矩阵的最左上角
corresponds to the activation of the
对应于激活单元，
first hidden unit on the first training
它是位于第一个训练样本上的第一个隐藏单元
example on one value down corresponds to
它的下一个值对应于
the activation in the second hidden unit
第二个隐藏单元的激活值
on the first training example then the
它是位于第一个训练样本上的，
third hidden unit on the first training
以及第一个训练示例中第三个隐藏单元
example and so on so as you scan down
等等 所以当你扫描下来，
this is new indexing into the hidden
这是你索引到隐藏单位的数字，
units number whereas you move
而如果你水平移动，
horizontally then you're going from the
那么你将从
first hidden unit the first training
第一个训练示例中从第一个隐藏的单元
example to now the first hidden unit the second
一直到现在第二个训练样本
training example the third training
第三个训练样本
example and so on until this node here
等等 直到这里的节点
corresponds to the activation of the
对应于 第一个隐藏单元的激活值
first hidden unit in the final training
而这隐藏单元是位于 这m个训练样本中的最终训练样本
example in the M training example ok so
所以
the horizontal the the matrix A goes
从水平上看，矩阵A
over at different training examples and
代表了我们不同的训练样本
vertically the different indices in the
而在竖直方向，矩阵A的不同的索引
matrix n corresponds to different hidden
对应于不同的隐藏单元
units and a similar intuition holds true
并且类似的情况
for the matrix Z as well as well for X
对于矩阵Z，X也是如此
where horizontally corresponds to
水平方向上对应于
different training examples and
不同的训练样本
vertically it corresponds to different
竖直方向上，它对应不同的
features different input features which
输入特征，
are really different note if a layer of the neural network
而这是神经网络输入层中不同的节点
so with these equations you now know how
所以，使用这些等式，你明白了
to implement in your network with
如何在你的神经网络上
vectorization that is vectorization
通过向量化来实现
across multiple examples
在多样本情况下的向量化
in the next video I want to show you a
在下一个是视频当中，我将向你展示
bit more justification about why this is
一些验证，这些验证主要是针对于为什么
a correct implementation of this type of
这是一种正确向量化的实现
vectorization it turns out the
结果证明
justification will be similar to whether
这种验证将会与你
you have seen for logistic regression
在逻辑回归当中所见到的很相似
let's go on to the next video
让我们进入下一个视频中吧